{
    "id": "954ae2397e0a4ccea7d9854a3f6d28cb",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you know for sure or is it only ………………………….?",
            "description": "Conjecture means guess work.",
            "answers": [
                "conjecture",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a vast difference between infatuation and ……………………………… love.",
            "description": "Conjugal means married.",
            "answers": [
                "conjugal",
                "congenital",
                "conjured"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The couple celebrated their 10th anniversary of ………………………………. love.",
            "description": "Either conjugal or connubial can be used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "conjugal",
                "connubial",
                "congenital"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………………………… worker arrives on time and leaves no mess behind him.",
            "description": "Conscientious means responsible, ethical and dutiful.",
            "answers": [
                "conscious",
                "conscientious",
                "conscience"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy’s ………………………………. would not let him lie.",
            "description": "Conscience means moral sense.",
            "answers": [
                "conscious",
                "conscience",
                "conscientious"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Were you ………………………………. of his hostility?",
            "description": "Conscious means aware.",
            "answers": [
                "conscious",
                "conscientious",
                "conscience"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The public must learn to ……………………………… electricity.",
            "description": "Conserve means use sparingly.",
            "answers": [
                "conserve",
                "converse"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was very …………………………………. of you to send me a get-well card.",
            "description": "Considerate means thoughtful.",
            "answers": [
                "considerable",
                "considerate",
                "considering"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "To their complete ……………………………. the swimmers saw a shark approaching.",
            "description": "Consternation means  shock or terror",
            "answers": [
                "conspiration",
                "constellation",
                "consternation"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His limp is ………………………………..",
            "description": "Either constitutional or congenital can be used here ",
            "answers": [
                "constitutional",
                "congenital",
                "institutional"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Chicken pox is a ………………………………… disease.",
            "description": "Contagious means infectious.",
            "answers": [
                "contagious",
                "contiguous",
                "contingent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The unusually heavy rainfall was an ………………………….. omen for the travelers",
            "description": "Ill can mean unfavorable or inauspicious. ",
            "answers": [
                "ill",
                "sick",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}